Emrullah Yaprak

- O Dublin, Ireland
- **%** (+90) 5364923401
- @ yaprakemrullah22@gmail.com
- emrullahyaprak.com
- github.com/eyaprak
- www.linkedin.com/in/emrullah-yaprak/

SUMMARY

I am currently living in Dublin, Ireland. I'm a student at an English school located in Dublin, and I am studying there every day until 12.30 p.m and I have a Stamp 1 visa type. So I can only work for 20 hours each week. I have more than 5 years of experience in Web Development. I used to develop applications with PHP, Flutter, Oracle PL/SQL, Wordpress etc. I have been working with React.js, Next.js, Node.js, MongoDB and many other technologies until December 2020. During this time, I have created projects that can be viewed in my portfolio website. One of them, developed using Flutter and published it on Google Play.

WORK EXPERIENCE

December 2020-Current

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

- **■** FREELANCER
- Dublin, Ireland
- I have been working with Node.js, Express.js, React.js, Next.js, MongoDB, Tailwindcss, MaterialUI, Redux and many other technologies until December 2020. In this process, I have created many projects that can be viewed in the my portfolio website.

June 2019-December 2020

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- **B** GENEX SOFTWARE INC
- Istanbul, Turkey
- Used HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, NODE.JS and created responsive pages in Oracle Apex.
- · Used Node.js to got datas from API in Oracle Apex and created few IG with this data.
- Designed application framework and developed Oracle APEX Application.
- Converted Oracle Forms pages to Oracle Apex pages.
- Prepare plugins on the Oracle Apex system.
- Worked with Sql Developer managed data and tables.
- Created various DML and DDL statements using PL/SQL and SQL.
- Installed and updated Oracle Apex Dashboard product on clients.
- · Worked closely with clients to establish problem specifications and system designs.
- Used Wordpress system to build websites.
- Managed and kept the Wordpress website of the company updated.

- Inserted products on websites and managed products price, description and other requirements.
- Shared products on market places and kept them up-to-date.

November 2016-March 2017

WEB DEVELOPER

- **E** COŞKUN YAYINCILIK INC
- Istanbul, Turkey
- Used HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT and PHP programing languages.
- · Used Wordpress system to build websites.
- · Managed and kept the Wordpress website of the company updated.
- Inserted products on websites and managed products price, description and other requirements.
- Shared products on market places and kept them up-to-date.

June 2016-August 2016

INTERNSHIP

- **MERCEDES BENZ TURK INC**
- Istanbul, Turkey
- I saw an internship for 60 working days in the human resources department at Mercedes-Benz Türk A.Ş.

July 2014-September 2014

Sales Manager

- **B** AYFA PRESS & BROADCAST DISTRIBUTION INC
- Istanbul, Turkey

EDUCATION

2015-2019

Bachelor's in COMPUTER ENGINEERING

- Duzce University
- O Düzce, Turkey

Bachelor's in COMPUTER ENGINEERING Duzce University

September 2015 to June 2019

COMPUTER ENGINEERING

SKILLS

API HTML Javascript Javascript Frameworks and Libraries Node.JS React PHP

Software Engineer Structured Software Development DDL Oracle Oracle Forms PL/SQL SQL CSS APEX Mongodb Wordpress Sales Manager

LANGUAGES

English - Intermediate Turkish - Fluent

WORK AUTHORISATION

I am authorised to work in the following countries:

Ireland